let questions = [
    {
      "question": "What company created Kali Linux",
      "option1": "Offensive Security",
      "option2": "Canonical",
      "option3": "Kali Linux,",
      "option4": "Debian",
      'answer': "1",
    },
  
    {
      "question": "What stand for DDOS",
      "option1": "Denial of Domain Servie",
      "option2": "Docker Domain Out Service",
      "option3": "Distributed denial of service",
      "option4": "Denial Of Service attack",
      'answer': "3",
    },
  
    {
      "question": "What is the NMap",
      "option1": "Password cracker ",
      "option2": "Network Mapper",
      "option3": "Wireless attack",
      "option4": "All of them",
      'answer': "2",
    },
  
    {
      "question": "What is aircrack-ng used for",
      "option1": "Network Mapper",
      "option2": "to detect weak passwords",
      "option3": "Wireless weakness",
      "option4": "to crack WEP and WPA/WPA2-PSK keys",
      'answer': "4",
    },
  
    {
      "question": " What are the components of Linux?",
      "option1": "Hardware",
      "option2": "Kernel",
      "option3": "Shell,",
      "option4": "All of them",
      'answer': "4",
    },
  
    {
      "question": " What are the pen-testing methodologies?",
      "option1": "Black-Box Testing",
      "option2": "White-Box Testing",
      "option3": "Gray-Box Testing",
      "option4": "All of them",
      'answer': "4",
    },
  
    {
      "question": "What is John the Ripper used for",
      "option1": "Pentesting website",
      "option2": "Password cracking",
      "option3": "Hacking mobile phone",
      "option4": "None of them",
      'answer': "2",
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the main 3 types of hackers?",
      "option1": "Black hats, white hats and grey hats",
      "option2": "Red hats, Green hats and Script hats",
      "option3": "Blue hats, script hats and grey hats",
      "option4": "none of them",
      'answer': "1",
    },

    {
      "question": "What can't you do with Linux?",
      "option1": "Run Windows programs",
      "option2": "Play games ",
      "option3": "Get viruses ",
      "option4": " Take some bus resources away from an existing device and assign the existing device alternative bus-resources that it can use instead (yet).",
      'answer': "4",
    },

    {
      "question": "What animal represents Linux?",
      "option1": "Tux the Penguin",
      "option2": "Bob the Mandrake ",
      "option3": "Bill the evil bat of greeds ",
      "option4": " George the Wombat.",
      'answer': "1",
    },
    
    
  ];
  